pokemonworldonline.net 2016-09-02

# Privacy Policy · Pokémon World Online

[Register Free](http://playerdex.pokemon-world-online.net/register.php) Download the Game [Forums](http://forum.pokemon-world-online.net/) [Playerdex](http://playerdex.pokemon-world-online.net/) [Wiki](http://pwo-wiki.info/) [View Updates from Twitter](https://twitter.com/PWO_/timelines/572545499917627392)

Your personal information and privacy are important to Pokémon World Online. Establishing and maintaining a trusting relationship between our service and our players is crucial to the success of our games, and this Privacy Policy has been created and enforced with the intent of allowing our users to feel comfortable and safe while participating in our services.

If you feel that Pokémon World Online are not abiding by its posted policies, you should contact an Administrator via the Pokémon World Online Forums.

Personal Information is information that someone would be able to use to contact or identify you. This includes information such as your full name, telephone number, or email address. Personal Information does not include compiled data that by itself cannot be used to identify an individual person (such as the percentage of users that hail from a specific country).

This Privacy Policy is a part of our End-User License Agreement and Terms of Service Agreements, and by participating in any portion of the service you agree to be bound by its terms and conditions. This Privacy Policy only addresses activities conducted within our services. Any other website or service (including those to which we may link) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed, controlled, or influenced by this policy.

## I Collection of Personal Information

You provide certain Personal Information, such as your email address, upon registering with the Pokémon World Online service, sending support emails to Pokémon World Online, and via completion of forms or other questionnaires sent to us.

## II How Personal Information May be Used

Any Personal Information submitted to Pokémon World Online may be used by Pokemon World Online for a variety of reasons, within reasonable limitation.

This information may be used to identify rightful possession of an account in the event of a lost or stolen password. This information may be used to identify multiple accounts as falling under the possession of one individual. This information may be used to prevent those in possession of terminated accounts future access to the service. This information may be used to provide optional email updates from either our website or forums, at the sole discretion of you, the user. This information may be used to verify the status of a donation made to Pokemon World Online.

In the highly unlikely event that legal authorities request Pokemon World Online provide such Personal Information for use in any legal context, Pokémon World Online will be required to oblige the requests of such authorities.

This information may not and will not be shared with any third party source, with the exception of law enforcement officials as previously noted. This information may not and will not be sold to any third party source. This information may not and will not be gathered unwillingly or without the knowledge of its provider under any circumstance; all information collected by Pokémon World Online must be consented by its source.

## III Child Protection

In order to protect the privacy interests of minors, we do not allow children under the age of 18 to participate in any service provided by Pokémon World Online, including forums and game, without the consent of a parent or guardian.

## IV Accessing an Account

Pokemon World Online staff may be required to access your account. This access is required for our services to identify any errors and monitor suspicious activity.

  * For the game, staff may be required to monitor your activity. Private messages cannot be viewed and your password will not be required.
  * For the Playerdex, you will be asked for permission for staff to access your account. Staff should not require your password.

## V Protection of Personal Information

Pokémon World Online take necessary precautions to protect our users' information; any information willingly provided to Pokémon World Online is protected both online and offline.

We have established and maintain reasonable security procedures to protect the confidentiality and integrity of your Personal Information. Encryption and other security measures (such as but not limited to off-site backup and password protection), as well as any combination of such practices, are used by Pokémon World Online to help provide our users with adequate security in regards to private data.

The number of individuals who have access to any Personal Information collected by Pokémon World Online is limited to a very small number of people, and our staff is routinely updated and debriefed as our security practices develop and evolve. Staff will be limited in the type of Personal Information they can access depending on the access level the staff member has.

By participating in any portion of any service provided by Pokémon World Online, including forums and game, you acknowledge that "perfect security" does not exist on the internet and that Pokémon World Online will execute to the fullest extent of their power the best security and protection possible to ensure the integrity of your Personal Information.

If you have any questions about the security provided by the service, you can contact an Administrator on the Pokémon World Online Forums.

Advertisement

Advertisement
